Hi everyone, my name is Iman. Today I want to give you a
demo of Thursday prototype of an agent that you can control
just through your voice and that you can use to both
control your operating system as well as writing
applications. Thursday, are you with us?
Yeah, come here ready to help with whatever is on your
screen.
Now I would really like you to bring up the Calculator app.
On it.
Now calculator is open. Please calculate 5 + 5.
One SEC.
5 + 5 is 10.
Thank you for confirming this. Can you switch back to
Safari please?
Switching back now.
So you can see that you can see that the agent is able to
control the operating system. It actually cascades down the
commands. There is a fast session and then that fast
session is built using GPD 5.6 Lunar. So it's really fast
for like single commands that you just saw. And then there
is a deep session that you can use for more complex tasks
that will run in the background. And the real time model
will actually be notified whenever there is a new event
from both sessions.
So can you quickly build an open street map? Demo
application can be done in a single file of the top five
points of interest on Crete.
Sure, I'll put that together.
Now while this is building that single file demo in the
background.
All right, writing the HTML file now.
Now, while this is building, can you bring up tomorrow's
weather in a new window?
Sure, checking.
OK, tomorrow's Weather for Crete is open in a new Safari
tab.
Please switch to it.
Switching now.
Alright, I'm on the weather tab and the demo file is still
getting put together.
Ah, I see you've opened it. Amazing. Can you give me a
quick walk through how this works?
Yeah, totally. The page shows an interactive open street
map centered on Create. Let me just make this a bit easier
to see. Hmm. OK, there we go. It's a simple Leaflet map
with markers. Each marker is one of the top five spots, and
you can Click to see a little more about each. It's
updating right now.
Give me a second.
OK, it's ready. The Create Explorer page shows 5 must see
spots on an interactive map. Click on marker to see a short
blurb and tips for visiting.
Alright, can you bring up point #5 for me?
Sure. Well, let me pull it up.
There it is .5 is Spinalonga, A fortified Venetian island
near Ilunda with layers of history and boat access you can
check before going. Amazing, Thank you so much for this
coding work.